let questions = [

{
    numb:1,
    question:"Who developed the bootstrap?",
    answer:"D.Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton",
    options:[
    "A. James Gosling",
    "B. Mark Jukervich",
    "C. Dennis Ritchie",
    "D. Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton",
       ]
    },

{
    numb:2,
    question:"Is Bootstrap3 mobile-first?",
    answer:"A. True",
    options:[
    "A. True",
    "B. False",
    "C. Can't say",
    "D. May be",
]
    },

{
    numb:3,
    question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to provide a responsive fixed width container?",
    answer:"A. .container-fixed",
    options:[
    "A. .container-fixed",
    "B. .container-fluid",
    "C. .container",
    "D. All of the above",
]
    },


{
    numb:4,
    question:"How many coloumns are allowed in a bootstrap grid system?",
    answer:"B. 12",
    options:[
    "A. 2",
    "B. 12",
    "C. 3",
    "D. 5",
]
    }, 

{
    numb:5,
    question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create  a bigbox for calling extra attention?",
    answer:"D. .jumbotron",
    options:[
    "A. .box",
    "B. .container",
    "C. .container-fluid",
    "D. .jumbotron",
]
    },

{
    numb:6,
    question:"Which of the below bootstrap class is used to convert image to circle ?",
    answer:"B. .img-circle",
    options:[
    "A. .img-rounded ",
    "B. .img-circle",
    "C. .img-rounded ",
    "D. None of the above"
]
    },

{
    numb:7,
    question:"How do we create the dropdown menu in bootstrap ?",
    answer:"C. .dropdown",
    options:[
    "A..select-list",
    "B. .select",
    "C. .dropdown",
    "D. None of the above",
]
    },

{
    numb:8,
    question:"Which of the following class is used to create a black navigation bar?",
    answer:"B. .navbar-inverse",
    options:[
    "A. .navbar-default",
    "B. .navbar-inverse",
    "C. .navbar-black",
    "D. .navbar-dark",
]
    },

{
    numb:9,
    question:"The plugin used to create a cycle trought elments as a slideshow is -?",
    answer:"C. carousel",
    options:[
    "A. slideshow",
    "B. scrollspy",
    "C. carousel",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
    },
    
    
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a dropdown menu?",
        answer:"A. .dropdown",
        options:[
        "A. .dropdown",
        "B. .select",
        "C. .select-list",
        "D. None of the above",
        ]
        },



    {
        numb:11,
        question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create  a basic list group?",
        answer:"C. .list=group",
        options:[
        "A. .grouped-list",
        "B. .select-list",
        "C. .list=group",
        "D. .list-grouped",
    ]
    },

{
    numb:12,
    question:"The class used to shape an image to a circle is -?",
    answer:"B. .img-circle",
    options:[
    "A. .img-rounded",
    "B. .img-circle",
    "C. .img-rounded",
    "D. .None of gthe above",
]
},


{
    numb:13,
    question:"Which of the follwing class in bootstrap is used to add a zebra-stripe to a table?",
    answer:"D. .tab-striped",
    options:[
    "A. .tab-striped",
    "B. .zebra-strip",
    "C. .table-stripped",
    "D. .table-striped",
]
},

{
    numb:14,
    question:"Which of the following  class in bootstrap is used to create a large button?",
    answer:"D. .btn-lg",
    options:[
    "A. .btn-xl.",
    "B. .btn-lrg",
    "C. .btn-large",
    "D. .btn-lg",
]
},

{
    numb:15,
    question:"Which of the following plugin in bootstrap is used to create a modal window?",
    answer:"C. .modal",
    options:[
    "A . .popup",
    "B. .alert",
    "C. .modal",
    "D. .window",
]
},

{
    numb:16,
    question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create basic pagination?",
    answer:"D. .pagination",
    options:[
    "A. .page",
    "B. .pagin",
    "C. .paginate",
    "D. .pagination",
]
},

{
    numb:17,
    question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a badge?",
    answer:"B. .badge",
    options:[
    "A. .tag",
    "B. .badge",
    "C. .page",
    "D. .flag",
]
},

{
    numb:18,
    question:"The class in bootstrap used to provide rounded corners to the image is -?",
    answer:"D. .img-rounded",
    options:[
    "A..img-circle",
    "B. .image-circle",
    "C. .image-rounded",
    "D. .img-rounded",
]
},

{
    numb:19,
    question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a panel?",
    answer:"A. .panel",
    options:[
    "A. .panel",
    "B. .container",
    "C. .box",
    "D. .jumbotron",
    ]
},

{
    numb:20,
    question:"Using which of the following, we can create a pager in bootstrap?",
    answer:"C. .pager",
    options:[
    "A. .carousel",
    "B. .collapse",
    "C. .pager",
    "D. .None of the above",
]
}

];